<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AHZ</title>
    
    
    
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on AHZ</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying Solidity Wargames: Smarx&#39;s capture the ether</title>
      <link>/post/demystifying-solidity-wargames-smarxs-capture-the-ether/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/demystifying-solidity-wargames-smarxs-capture-the-ether/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;img src=&#34;/img/Demystifying-solidity-wargames-smarx-capture-the-ether/cover.png&#34;/&gt;
          
        
        
        
          In this write-up, I will demystify how to conquer the Smarx&#39;s capture the ether wargame.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying Solidity Wargames: Openzeppelin&#39;s ethernaut</title>
      <link>/post/demystifying-solidity-wargames-openzeppelins-ethernaut/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/demystifying-solidity-wargames-openzeppelins-ethernaut/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;img src=&#34;/img/Demystifying-solidity-wargames-openzeppelin-ethernaut/cover.jpg&#34;/&gt;
          
        
        
        
          In this write-up, I will demystify how to conquer the Openzeppelin&#39;s ethernaut wargame.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THE GRINCH NETWORKS IS DOWN!</title>
      <link>/post/the-grinch-networks-is-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-grinch-networks-is-down/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;img src=&#34;/img/THE-GRINCH-NETWORKS-IS-DOWN%21/cover.png&#34;/&gt;
          
        
        
        
          After 28 days of non-stop hacking, I was announced as the winner of Hackerone&#39;s Hackyholidays 2020-2021, In this write-up, I will explain how I was able to break the grinch networks down, for once and for all!
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chaining vulnerabilities leads to account takeover</title>
      <link>/post/chaining-vulnerabilities-leads-to-account-takeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/chaining-vulnerabilities-leads-to-account-takeover/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;img src=&#34;/img/Chaining-vulnerabilities-leads-to-account-takeover/cover.png&#34;/&gt;
          
        
        
        
          In this write-up, I will explain how I was able to chain five vulnerabilities that led to one link click account takeover.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bypassing OTP via reset password</title>
      <link>/post/bypassing-otp-via-reset-password/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/bypassing-otp-via-reset-password/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;img src=&#34;/img/Bypassing-OTP-via-reset-password/cover.jpg&#34;/&gt;
          
        
        
        
          In this write-up, I will explain how I was able to bypass one-time password by resetting the password via email address.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          While protecting the decentralized economy is protecting the pioneering blockchain industry, and protecting the open economy is protecting the decentralized economy, The missions aim diverge and is observed through different points, Such that protecting the open economy is democratizing observation where whole systems and entities tends to participate due to the clear open routes and agreed upon policies, And while protecting the decentralized economy is protecting a form or a route of the open economy, The decentralized economy special features and distinct nature creates special problems, Where distinguishing the special route of the open economy wouldn&amp;rsquo;t situate nor rebound the critical issues, By redefining the decentralized economy as connective route that rebase the open economy and respire the inefficient routes we will create a world where the decentralized economy saturate and cultivate the incompetent entities, Not only freeing those entities but circulating more fair value of the open economy process, And the blockchain industry is pioneering by providing high-quality cut-edge self-assurance technologies that are rampantly growing as the core of the world we&amp;rsquo;re presenting, unique or lacking distinction, Protecting this technology is the principle.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archive</title>
      <link>/archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/archive/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>